

João Pinto

Nationality: Portuguese

(+351) 939048142

Date of birth: 02/06/1995

Gender: Male

Email address: joao11diogomoita@gmail.com

Address: Rua Beata D.Mafalda Ent.218 Casa 41, 4350-221 Porto (Portugal)

ABOUT ME

João likes technologies since he was a child, he always has been fascinated about everything that relates that specific area. He loves to play computer and search about the most diverse topics, a true curious. Recently, about two years ago he found out a passion for programming and logic. Since then he has been dedicated to study programming. Now as a student of Specialist technical in technologies and programming he is ready to new challenges and practice his knowledge in the area, he is excited to learn, grow professionally and exchange experiences.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Specialist technical in technologies and programming

CINEL [06/2020 - Current]

Address: Rua de São Rosendo, 377, 4300-478 Porto (Portugal)

www.cinel.pt

Level in EQF: EQF level 5

Formative course of informatic

IEFP [01/2015 – 05/2015]

Address: R. Peso da Régua, 4300-409 Porto (Portugal)

Sociocultural animator certification

Escola Secundária Alexandre Herculano [09/2011 - 07/2014]

Address: Avenida Camilo, 4300-096 Porto (Portugal)

Level in EQF: EQF level 4

WORK EXPERIENCE

shelf filler

Leroy Merlin [07/2019 - 01/2020]

City: Porto

Country: Portugal

- -Replacement of all types of bricolage materials
- -Organization and maintenance of workspace

Sales assistant

LIDL [09/2016 - 05/2019]

City: Porto

Country: Portugal

- -Cashier, exchanges and returns.
- -Meat, bakery and retail replacement.
- -Organization and maintenance of workspace.

Counter employee

Churrasqueira rotunda da Boavista [11/2015 - 06/2016]

City: Porto

Country: Portugal

- Counter service.
- Replacement, maintenance and cleaning of workspace.
- Take away service.

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s):

Portuguese

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B2 READING B2 WRITING A2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1

DIGITAL SKILLS

Informatic Knowledge

Microsoft Teams / Quick learner on new softwares / Gmail / Cloud Storage / Solid computer skills in user view / Outlook / Microsoft Office

Programming

Basic knowledge in UML Methodolegy / MySQL / Basic knowledge of PHP programming language / Basic C Langage / Java / HTML & CSS - Basic / Python

Personal skills

Proactive / Motivation to grow professionally / Analytic skills / Motivation to Learn. / Motivation to learn coding / Team-Work Oriented

COMMUNICATION AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Social capacities

-Great capacity to communicate with anyone, through a few years of experience on client service and with the certification of Sociocultural animator.

DRIVING LICENCE

Driving Licence: B